Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and 
typesetting industry. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's
 standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an 
 unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled 
 it to make a type specimen book. It has survived not 
 only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic 
 typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged. It was 
 popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset 
 sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more 
 recently with desktop publishing software like Aldus 
 PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.
